http://youngactorsspace.com/privacy-policy/

SIGN IN YOUR ACCOUNT TO HAVE ACCESS TO DIFFERENT FEATURES
USERNAME
PASSWORD
Remember Me
FORGOT YOUR PASSWORD?
FORGOT YOUR DETAILS?
USERNAME OR EMAIL
PRIVACY POLICY
Youngactorsspace.com Privacy Policy:
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
• To quickly process your transactions.
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
How do we protect your information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
• Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
• Help the website run faster the next time you visit.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, It won't affect the user's experience.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party links
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
• Remarketing with Google AdSense
• Google Display Network Impression Reporting
• Demographics and Interests Reporting
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal information:
• By emailing us
• By calling us
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We market to
We do not collect information from children under 13
children under 13.
No
In order to remove your child's information please contact the following personnel:
Young Actors Space, LLC
info@youngactorsspace.com
We adhere to the following COPPA tenants:
• Parents can review, delete, manage or refuse with whom their child's information is shared through contacting us directly.
or contacting us directly.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify you via email
• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
youngactorsspace.com
5918 Van Nuys Blvd.
Sherman Oaks, California 91401
United States
info@youngactorsspace.com
818-785-7979
Last Edited on 2018-06-19
LET'S GET STARTED!
REGISTER FOR CLASS
SCHEDULE COACHING
RENT THE SPACE
DOWNLOAD THE GUIDE
young_actors_space
young_actors_space
Calling
all
teen
actors!
Join
us
this
weekend
for
...
View
Dec 2
Open
young_actors_space
January
through
March
online
acting
classes
at
YAS...
View
Nov 12
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
actress
@brandilyn_cheah
in
...
View
Nov 11
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
actor
@camdivineengels
in
the
latest
...
View
Nov 7
Open
young_actors_space
Our
artistic
director
Patrick
Day
(@pactorick)is
...
View
Nov 2
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
actor
@willmeyersofficial
in
the
new
...
View
Oct 17
Open
young_actors_space
Hear
#YAS
actress
@victoriagraceactress
as
...
View
Oct 16
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
alum
@karanbrar
in
the
new
film
Hubie
...
View
Oct 9
Open
young_actors_space
Check
out
the
new
book
"Top
Hollywood
Acting
...
View
Oct 9
Open
young_actors_space
Even
more
@sabrinacarpenter
news
today
--
catch
...
View
Oct 8
Open
young_actors_space
Congrats
to
#YAS
alum
@sabrinacarpenter,
who
was
...
View
Oct 7
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
actor
@camdivineengels
in
the
new
film
...
View
Oct 7
Open
young_actors_space
Congrats
to
#YAS
alum
@baileynoble11
on
the
...
View
Oct 6
Open
young_actors_space
Congrats
to
#YAS
actress
@juliette.hanover
on
...
View
Oct 1
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
actor
Aidan
Singh
in
the
new
film
...
View
Sep 26
Open
young_actors_space
New
online
classes
at
#YAS
start
this
weekend,
and...
View
Sep 22
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
actress
@officialmarionvancuyck
...
View
Sep 20
Open
young_actors_space
Catch
#YAS
alum
@emilymest
on
the
new
@netflix
...
View
Sep 19
Open
young_actors_space
Have
you
received
our
FREE
resource
guide
yet?
...
View
Sep 10
Open
young_actors_space
New
classes
start
next
week!
For
more
information
...
View
Sep 8
Open
Load More...
Join Us On Instagram!
RELAX | LISTEN | REACT
(818) 785-7979 | info@youngactorsspace.com
5918 Van Nuys Blvd., Sherman Oaks, CA 91401
Young Actors Space is bonded with the State of California and all instructors have a Child Performer Services Permit. |  Bond # W150220962
Copyright © 2018 Young Actors Space | All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy | Attendance Policy
ABOUT
ALUMNI
CLASS
SUMMER
COACH
THE SPACE
RESOURCES
FAQ
Young Actors Space@YoungActorsSpc·28 Jun 2018We are having such an awesome week with this terrific group of young actors during our 5th Annual On-Camera Conservatory! We can't wait to start filming their scenes tonight. Great work everyone! #Actor #ActorsLife #ChildActor #Acting #Camp #SummerCamp #YoungActorsSpace Reply on Twitter 1012410443409784832Retweet on Twitter 1012410443409784832Like on Twitter 1012410443409784832Twitter 1012410443409784832
TOP
